

.NET DEVELOPER

#### **Details**

Braga

Portugal

+351913526507

flaviojrjardim@gmail.com

#### Links

Portfolio/Personal WebSite

#### **Skills**

ASP.NET MVC

.NET Core	
C#	
SQL	
Git	

## Languages

Pidgin and creole - Portuguese based

Portuguese

English

#### **Profile**

I'm a Software Engineer with experience and extensive formation in software development and software design with strong skills on Microsoft Technology Stacks such as ASP.NET MVC, .NET Core, C# and SQL Server.

I think my best strengths are: determination, dedication, and responsibility. I'm always striving to bring 100% to the work that I do. Good communication and interpersonal skills. Good teamwork skills. I'm always available to help and learn. Critical thinking for problem-solving.

# **Employment History**

### Software Developer, e-Schooling, Braga

JANUARY 2020

Owner of the e-Schooling financial area development team, having as main responsibilities:

- -Develop and implement new features according to the business logic and needs of the company and customers, worked with SCRUM methodology;
- Analyze and resolve tasks to correct and/or eliminate errors and problems identified by customers;
- Provide technical support to the development team, contributing to an effective operational performance;
- Onboarding new teammates. Member of the e-Schooling financial area development team, having as main responsibilities: -Develop and implement new features according to the business logic and needs of the company and customers, worked with SCRUM methodology; Analyze and resolve tasks to correct and/or eliminate errors and problems identified by customers; Provide technical support to the development team, contributing to an effective operational performance; Onboarding new teammates.

**Technologies:** .NET Framework; ASP.NET MVC; ASP.NET Core; C#; Microsoft SQL Server; Scrum; JavaScript

## Junior Software Developer, PRIMAVERA Business Software Solution, Braga

DECEMBER 2018 - APRIL 2019

Integration into a development team for a PRIMAVERA cloud offering worked with SCRUM methodology.

Technologies: .NET Core; C#; Microsoft SQL Server; Scrum

## Associate Developer, PRIMAVERA Business Software Solution, Braga

APRIL 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

Owner of the PRIMAVERA Developers Network project. A project to connect the PRIMAVERA developers community.

#### Responsibilities:

- Code samples development for integration with GitHub;
- Interaction with development teams to placement technical content in the PRIMAVERA Developers Network;
- Dynamization of the community in forums (Internal and StackOverflow);
- Technical support.

Technologies: .NET Framework; C#; Microsoft SQL Server; Scrum; GIT

Frontend Developer, Solo PT, Porto

FEBRUARY 2017 - JUNE 2017

Internship based on MVP concept to build Web & Hybrid Apps development based on the Single Page applications concept for specific clients.

**Technologies:** Scrum; GIT; AngularJS; ECMAScript; SASS; HTML5

# **Education**

Computer Engineering, ISEP - Instituto Superior de Engenharia do Porto, Porto

SEPTEMBER 2008 - OCTOBER 2017

Final grade of the project/internship: 14/20